# **Gerry Ajie Pratama**

#### SUMMARY

Recently graduated from IT bootcamp of Glints x Binar Academy with specialization as Back End Developer. Skilled at creating restful API using Node.js and Express, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, using cloud services, and agile methods. Experienced in managing people and had ability to perform well in a team.. Experience as Scrum Master in the Final Project Bootcamp to manage 9 people.

# CONTACT



+6289519975297



gerryajie@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/gerryajie/



gitlab.com/gerryajie



Tangerang, Banten, Indonesia, 15112

# **EDUCATION**

Backend Developer Glints Academy Batch 15 Oct 2021- Jan 2022

Information Technology STIMIK Tulus Cendikia 2003 – 2008

#### **LANGUAGE**

**English**-Advance

Bahasa Indonesia-Native Speaker

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **Backend Developer Trainee in Glints Academy**

(Oct 2021 - )

- Successfully completed the final project, created an application called ChefBox using NodeJS as framework and JavaScript as programming language in 3 weeks.
- Implemented Express and Sequelize library for create the API.
- Acted as Scrum Master to lead 9 people and managed the project.

## **Operational Manager**

(June 2016 - April 2021)

- Directly report to CEO and BOD.
- Manage All Sales And Collector Including Admin.
- Make Sure good Environment.
- Be involved and participate in the overall operational lifecycle.
- Define and communicate technical and design requirements.
- Collaborate with a multidisciplinary team of designers, developers, and system administrators.

#### Credit Officer in PT. Bank Danamon Indonesia

(Jun 2014 - May 2016)

- Survey the Customer For lending up to 2 Billion Rupiah.
- Produced and provided analysis data of customer and the project progress for Micro lending.
- Make Approval for discount and Easy loan or reschedule for payment.

## **EXPERTISE**

Javascript

Node Js

**Express** 

SQL

Spreadsheet

Git

Npm

Sequelize-Cli

Excel

# **CERTIFICATION**

React Native Developer Bootcamp Glints Academy Aug 2021

CCNA Cisco Course Net Aug 2020

JavaScript Course Progate Aug 2021

#### Other Certification Links:

https://progate.com/course\_certificate/62b0c502qxerhx

# Credit Management Officer in Citibank

(Jun 2009 - May 2014)

- Managed Delinquent also Remedial Acc.
- Monitored reminder calls process from the Pre-Delinquent Desk Collectors resulted succeed maintain.
- credits flow rate below 7%, best achievement was 6% (improved by 32.5%).
- Collaborated in a team of 6 in analyzing and processing data resulted monthly performance report of each region in Indonesia.
- Coordinated with 3 Groups in Citibank to accelerate the collection process.

## **PORTFOLIO**

# **Backend Apllication**

• Glints Academy mini Project

Event For Meeting The Client and Announcement

Framework: NodeJS

Programming Language: JavaScript

Link application:

GitLab:

https://gitlab.com/binarxglints\_batch15/miniproject/team-c/backendteam\_c.git

• Glints Academy Final Project: ChefBox

**ChefBox** is an application/ website to help you find the Recipe for your every problem Serve the cook.

Framework: NodeJS

**Programming Language** : JavaScript **Middleware Library** : Sequelize-cli

Link application:

https://gitlab.com/binarxglints\_batch15/finalproject/chefbox/backend.git